Guide to the New York State Democratic Committee records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series IV: Ephemera, 1996-2007
  - Subseries IV.1: Printed Material, 1996-2007
    - New Yorkers for Kerry and Edwards, 2004 (oversize) (Box 37)
    - Presidential Print Awarded to Clinton by the DNC, 1996 (oversize) (Box 35)
    - Support the Democratic Ticket! Kerry/Edwards/Schumer, 2004 (oversize) (Box 37)
    - Victory 2001 (oversize) (Box 37)
    - Victory 2002 NYSD Convention (oversize) (Box 37)
    - Victory 2002 NYSD Convention (oversize) (Box 40)
  - Subseries IV. 2: Realia, 1996-2004
    The materials in this subseries include buttons, pins, and bumper stickers that show support for the Democratic party as a whole and for specific candidates like Hillary Rodham Clinton, Al Gore, and John Kerry.
    - Clinton and Gore and Moynhihan Bumper Stickers (Box 1)
    - Clinton and Gore button, 1996 (Box 38)
    - John Kerry President button, 2004 (Box 38)
    - Miriam Haskell Co. pin, Honoring Hillary Rodham Clinton and Tipper Gore, undated (Box 38)
    - New York State Democratic Committee Flag pin, undated (Box 38)
    - NY 2004 Democrats, 2004 (Box 38)
    - Victory! New York State Democratic Committee pin, undated (Box 38)
    - Vote Democrat: McCall, Mehiel, Hevesi, Spitzer button, 2002 (Box 38)